Jesus Medina

Cell: (909) 362-0293 | 005172852@coyote.csusb.edu | jesusdmedina.com

Summary

Computer System major, with an emphasis in system administration. Experience using popular IT automation tools along with scripting in bash to configure several servers. Experience with building websites in HTML and CSS. Experience in application development using Apple's programming language Swift. Experience in troubleshooting computers, tablets, and office equipment as well as open-repair for electronic devices.

Highlights

- Excellent Coordinating Skills
- Problem Solver
- Excellent Research Skills
- Great Communication Skills
- Excellent Organization

Skills

- C++
- Python
- HTML, CSS
- JavaScript
- Ansible
- Swift
- Bash
- Programming in Arduino

Accomplishments

- Demonstrated strong communication skills through networking and taking part in instructing
- Build personal resume website in HTML and CSS
- Successfully used Ansible to automate remote clients

Experience

IT Student Intern, Marshall Elementary School - San Bernardino, CA | 04/2017 - present

- Administrator for SBCUSD Mobile Mosyle at Marshall Elementary
- Administrator for SBCUSD Accelerated Reader Marshall Elementary
- Test Examiner for TELL and California English Language Development Test at Marshall Elem.
- Open and repair iPads and Mac computers
- Work with the Alexandria system for the library
- Troubleshoot printers, SMART Board Projectors, and other office equipment

Lead Instructor, Electronic Assembler, Kids That Code, Inc - San Bernardino, CA | 02/2019 - present

- Instructor for several game development class consisting of more 100 students
- Create programming curriculum to be taught by instructors
- Soldering micro-processing units to be used for autonomous robot creation

Technical Support, Help Desk Technician, CyberTech Software & Systems - San Bernardino, CA | 08/2019 - present

- Provide customer support for SBCUSD students and parents
- Inventory and asset checkout

Vendor Verification & Compliance, Burlington Warehouse - Redlands, CA | 06/2018 - 09/2018

- Inspecting products and understanding SKU information
- Inspecting cartons by using RF scanners
- Documenting passes and fails

Education

BA Computer Systems Administration

California State University: San Bernardino – San Bernardino, CA, United States

Expected 2020